30,000 fans. 300 cops. 1 serial killer. No escape.
Trap is a crime, horror, thriller film directed by M. Night Shyamalan.
A father and teen daughter attend a pop concert, where they realize
they're at the center of a dark and sinister event.
Cooper, played by Josh Hartnett.
Riley, played by Ariel Donoghue.
Lady Raven, played by Saleka Night Shyamalan.
Rachel, played by Alison Pill.
Dr. Josephine Grant, played by Hayley Mills.
Jamie, played by Jonathan Langdon.
Trap is a 2024 American thriller film produced, written, and directed by M.
Night Shyamalan.
The film stars Josh Hartnett, Ariel Donoghue, Shyamalan's
daughter Saleka Night, Hayley Mills, and Alison Pill.
The film follows Cooper Abbott, a serial killer known as the Butcher, who attends a concert with his teenage daughter Riley,
only to discover the event has been intercepted by police who have been tipped off that he would be present.
The film was shot in Canada in late 2023.
It premiered in New York City on July 24, 2024, and was
theatrically released in the United States by Warner Bros.
Pictures on August 2, 2024.
It received mixed reviews from critics and grossed
$83 million on a $30 million budget.
The film explores themes of concert, philadelphia,
pennsylvania, double life, escape, s.w.a.t..
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.